<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jinjie LI</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jinjie LI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Development of a 3D Simulator for Large-Scale Heterogeneous Swarm Robots</title>
      <link>/posts/potato/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/potato/</guid>
      <description>Overview This project is required to develope a simulator that supports (1) over 1000 robot nodes, (2) 6-DoF dynamic models of four model types, including fixed-wing UAVs, quadcopters, tilt-rotor UAVs, and vehicles, (3) range of vision and collision, (4) 3D visualization, and (5) a dataset to build for off-line model training and an interface with Gym for on-line DRL training.
The project is still undergoing. Some functions are displayed below.
1000 aircrafts detection follow </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing and Optimization of a Solar Aircraft</title>
      <link>/posts/solar_aircraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/solar_aircraft/</guid>
      <description>Overview Duration: Mar. 2018 - Oct. 2018
This project was designed for the Solar Aircraft project in the 2018 China Aeromodelling Design Challenge (CADC) competition. During this project, we designed and manufactured an aircraft with an empty weight between 2 and 3 kg, which relies entirely on solar panels for power. The aircraft must take off in a slipping manner.
In this project, I was responsible for the production of the wing spar and acted as the PILOT to fly the airplane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing and Optimization of Heavy Load and High Maneuverability Aircrafts (Composite material part)</title>
      <link>/posts/3kg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/3kg/</guid>
      <description>Overview Duration: Jul. 2017 - Oct. 2018
This project was designed for the Time-limited Airdrop Project in the 2018 China Aeromodelling Design Challenge competition (Participants of CADC came from nearly 100 universities in China). Our three flight groups won the first 🥇, second 🥈, and third 🥉 places, thereby setting the best records in history. As the leader of the composite group, I led six members to complete the production of the D-box structures, wing spars, ailerons, and fairings of six aircrafts for each of the three flight groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development of a Settable Constant Temperature Controller</title>
      <link>/posts/water_tank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/water_tank/</guid>
      <description>Requirements Duration: Feb. 2018 - Jun. 2018
Design and manufacture a constant temperature control system that can be set to a specific temperature:
 Set the temperature in grades (at least three) The range of heat is from 50 to 100 degrees, and the error should not exceed ±5 degrees. (Score according to the accuracy) Use a cellphone to set and display the temperature. Powered by 220V AC.  Achievements We shot this video to present the functions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
